TEJAS KULKARNI

Pune, MH · + 91 8668969864 tejas.kulkarni66@gmail.com

Result-oriented professional with several years of experience in Banking and IT Services Industry. Immense Exposure in Talent Acquisition & Onboarding, Induction process, Training and Development. 5+ years of experience in Human Resources. 5+ years of experience in Business Process & Operations. Actively looking for job opportunities in the same and can join immediately.

EXPERIENCE

2021 - 2022

HR MIS EXECUTIVE, CREDENCE RESOURCE MANAGEMENT PVT LTD

- Preparation of required PAN India MIS reports to management as per prescribed timelines
- Prepare Daily Inventory Stock Report in Excel
- Preparing master database and MBR report, having knowledge of excel formulas of vlookup & hlookup and pivot table
- Updating daily interview tracker on real basis and coordinating with management for the interview process
- Assisting with training and onboarding processes.
- Writing job descriptions for new positions, and assisting with interview and recruitment processes.

2017 - 2021

HR EXECUTIVE, ASHNEO TECHNOLOGIES

- Administering all the hiring processes of new employees
- Ensuring all the employees comply with the HR policies
- Preparing Offer letter, Experience letter, Warning letter and issuing various Documents,
- Arranging training programs for staffs
- Coordinating for Daily interviews
- Preparing Job Descriptions for recruitment process
- Generating monthly salary using GreytHR software
- Creating salary structure and yearly appraisal process
- Ensuring all the employees comply with the HR policies
- Counseling employees as and when required

2015 - 2017

EXECUTIVE, INBOX OPS PVT LTD

- Generating revenue by sending offers on ISP like Gmail, Yahoo, AOL, Hotmail
- Analyzing and Creating best offers for customers.
- Preparing data file for revenue generation.

2012 - 2014

EXECUTIVE, MASTERCARD

- Monitoring Banking Transactions and Generate reports for every half hourly transaction
- Expertise Knowledge in preparing MIS, generating pins, processing SCR's.
- Good understanding of MS Excel using formulas, lookups, pivot. Worked on SQL database for monitoring and reporting transactions count to client for every hourly and half hourly report.
- Generating pins for credit card operations daily one thousand approximately. Ability to work in 24x7 environments, processing all the works in the given TAT.

EDUCATION

2006-2009

BCOM, GARWARE COLLEGE (YCMOU), PUNE

Specialization in Accounts & Finance

SKILLS

- MS Office (Word, Excel, Powerpoint)
- Good Communication (English, Hindi, Marathi)
- Internet Recruiting
- Full cycle Recruiting
- Familiarity with HR Management Systems
- Employee Counseling
- Business Operations

- Candidate Screening
- Accurate Shortlisting
- GreytHR
- Documentation
- Familiarity with Applicant Tracking Systems
- Induction Programs & Training
- Business Process Outsourcing